爸爸走了
Dad's gone now.
他希望我们继续他的事业
He wants us to pick up where he left off.
怎么样 我们一起去杀些凶鬼恶灵
So, what do you say we kill some evil sons of bitches.
惹点麻烦吧
And we raise a little hell?
（忆往昔）
她真名叫贝拉·塔伯特
Bela Talbot's her real name.
对你来说就很不幸了
Which means seriously bad luck for you.
她是猎人吗
Is she a hunter?
才不是呢
Pretty frigging far from a hunter.
我为特定客户获取一些独特的东西
I procure unique items for a select clientele.
我想你会发现那是我的
I think you'll find that belongs to me.
你不会开枪的
You're not gonna shoot anybody.
你有什么毛病
What the hell is wrong with you?
知道吗 我一直在努力保住你的命 迪恩
You know what? I'm busting my ass trying to keep you alive, Dean.
你却一副毫不在乎的样子
And you act like you couldn't care less.
说实话 我累了 萨姆
Truth is, I'm tired, Sam.
我不知道 感觉就像隧道尽头有了光亮
I don't know. It's like there's a light at the end of the tunnel.
那是地狱烈火 迪恩
That's hellfire, Dean.
随便了
Well, whatever.
你是我哥哥
You're my big brother.
我会为你做任何事
There's nothing I wouldn't do for you.
不管我需要做什么 我一定要帮你脱困
And I don't care what it takes. I'm gonna get you out of this.
我能为你做什么 萨姆
Well. What can I do for you, Sam?
你马上解除迪恩的交易
You can let Dean out of his deal right now.
我只是推销的
I'm just a saleswoman.
我也像其他人一样有老板
I got a boss like everybody.
合同在他手里
He holds the contract.
那你的老板是谁
Then who's your boss?
我不能告诉你
I can't tell you.
抱歉 萨姆
I'm sorry, Sam…
这事没有出路
but there's no way out of this one.
（如今）
[邪恶力量 第3季第6集]
离开枫泉镇我就一直在等
So I've been waiting since Maple Springs.
你有话要跟我说吗
You got something to tell me?
又没到你生日
It's not your birthday.
对
No.
卷发快乐吗
Happy perm?
哥们 我不知道
Dude, I don't know.
我不知道你在说什么
I have no idea what you're talking about.
柯尔特枪少了颗子弹
There's a bullet missing from the Colt.
想告诉我是怎么回事吗
Wanna tell me how that happened?
我知道不是我
I know it wasn't me,
所以除非你去射击非常邪恶的罐子了
so unless you were shooting at some incredibly evil cans…
- 迪恩 - 你去找她了 是吧
- Dean. - You went after her, didn't you?
十字路口恶魔 尽管我叫你别去了
The Crossroads Demon, after I told you not to.
是啊
Yeah, well.
你可能会害死自己的
You could have gotten yourself killed.
我没有
I didn't.
你打死了她
And you shot her.
她总是自作聪明
She was a smart-ass.
怎么 我摆脱交易了吗
So, what, does that mean I'm out of my deal?
如果我是 你不觉得我肯定早说了吗 迪恩
Don't you think I might have mentioned that little fact, Dean?
没有
No.
合同在其他人手里
Someone else holds the contract.
谁
Who?
她不肯说
She wouldn't say.
那我们最好查明是谁
Well, we should find out who.
当然了 我们的最佳线索
You know, of course, our best lead.
就是十字路口恶魔
would be the Crossroads Demon.
等一下
Wait a minute.
这不好笑
That's not funny.
是啊 不好笑
No, it's not.
那是个愚蠢的风险 你不该那么做的
It was a stupid frigging risk and you shouldn't have done it.
我不该那么做
I shouldn't have done it?
你是我哥哥 迪恩
You're my brother, Dean.
不管你做什么 我都会努力救你
No matter what you do, I'm gonna try and save you.
而且我绝不会为此道歉 好吗
And I'm sure as hell not gonna apologize for it, all right?
但我不懂
But I don't understand.
我已经跟其他警探说过这些了
I already went over all this with the other detectives.
是啊
Right, yes,
但我们是郡警局的
but see, we're with the Sheriff's Department…
不是警察局的
not the Police Department.
部门不同
Different departments.
凯斯太太
So, Mrs. Case…
拜托
Please,
喊我凯斯女士
Ms. Case.
好吧
Okay.
凯斯女士
Ms. Case…
是你发现了你侄女 是吧
you were the one who found your niece, correct?
我回到家
I came home,
她在淋浴里
she was in the shower.
淹死了
Drowned?
死因裁判官是这么说的
So the coroner says.
你倒是说
Now you tell me.
一个人怎么可能在淋浴里淹死
How can someone drown in a shower?
你觉得茜拉死前几天里的
How would you describe Sheila's behavior.
行为如何
on the days before her death?
她是否看上去害怕
I mean, did she seem frightened?
或是提过什么不寻常的事吗
Maybe she said something out of the ordinary, or…?
等等
Wait a minute.
你们是跟艾莉克丝合作的吧
You're working with Alex, aren't you?
是的 没错
Yep. Absolutely. That's…
艾莉克丝和我们 关系可铁了
Alex and us, we're like this.
你们怎么不说
Why didn't you say so?
艾莉克丝给了我好大安慰
Alex has been such a comfort.
但抱歉 我以为案子都结了
But I'm sorry, I thought the case was solved.
没有 还没有
Well, no. No, not yet.
- 这样啊 - 总之
- I see. - So, anyways,
我们刚刚在说你侄女
we were talking about your niece.
是的
Well, yes,
茜拉死前是提到过一件怪事
Sheila mentioned something quite strange before she died.
她说她看见了一艘船
She said she saw a boat.
一艘船
Boat?
对 前一刻还在 转眼就不见了
Yes, one minute it was there, then it was gone.
在她眼前凭空消失了
It just disappeared right before her eyes.
你觉得那会是
You think it could be a.
鬼船吗
ghost ship?
艾莉克丝觉得可能是鬼船
Alex thinks it could be a ghost ship.
嗯
Well…
是可能
could be.
好吧
Well…
如果我还能帮到你 你尽管说
you let me know if there's anything else I can do for you.
什么都行
Anything at all.
真是个老疯婆子
What a crazy old broad.
怎么 因为她相信鬼吗
Why, because she believes in ghosts?
看你啊 维护你女朋友
Look at you sticking up for your girlfriend,
你个熟女控
you cougar hound.
咬我啊
Bite me.
除非她先动口
Not if she bites you first.
这个艾莉克丝是谁 城里还有别的猎人吗
So who's this Alex? We got another player in town?
可能吧
Maybe, maybe not.
我们的工作还是不变
Doesn't change our job.
我们的推论是鬼船 是吧
And we're thinking ghost ship, right?
嗯 而且这一带
Yeah. It's not the first one.
不是第一次有人看到鬼船了
that's been sighted around here, either.
- 是吗 - 嗯
- Really? - Yeah,
每隔37年都会出现 准时准点 一艘
every 37 years, like clockwork, reports of a vanishing…
三桅高速帆船在海湾里忽隐忽现
three-mast clipper ship out in the bay.
每隔37年 便会出现一系列怪异的陆上溺亡事件
And every 37 years, a rash of weirdo dry-land drownings.
所以不管怎么回事 这才是个开始
So whatever's happening is just getting started?
嗯
Yeah.
传说是怎样的
What's the lore?
全世界都有看到老旧幽灵沉船的事件
There are apparitions of old wrecks sighted all over the world.
紫罗兰号 格里芬号 飞翔的荷兰人号
The S.S. Violet, the Griffon, the Flying Dutchman.
几乎都是死亡预兆
Almost all of them are death omens.
那是怎么个情况 你看到船
So what happens? You see the ship,
几小时后
and then a few hours later…
你就死翘翘了
you pucker up and kiss your ass goodbye?
差不多吧
Basically.
接下来怎么办
What's the next step?
我得确认是哪艘船
I gotta ID the boat.
应该不难
Shouldn't be too hard.
在海岸沉没的三桅高速帆船
I mean, how many three-mast clipper ships.
能有几艘啊
are wrecked off the coast?
这我也查了
I checked that too, actually.
150多艘
Over 150.
是啊
Yeah.
该死
Crap.
我们是把车停这里了吧
This is where we parked the car, right?
我记得是
I thought so.
我的车呢
Where's my car?
你给停车表投币了吗
Did you feed the meter?
当然了
Yes, I fed the meter.
萨姆 我的车呢 有人偷我车了吗
Sam, where's my car? Somebody stole my car?
冷静 迪恩
Calm down, Dean.
我冷静 有人偷了我的车
I am calmed down. Someone stole my…
迪恩
Dean.
放松 放松
Take it easy. Take it easy.
67年的英帕拉吗
The '67 Impala?
那是你的吗
Was that yours?
贝拉
Bela.
对不起
I'm sorry,
- 我让人把车拖走了 - 什么
- I had that car towed. - You what?
车停在拖走区里了
Well, it was in a tow-away zone.
才没有
No, it wasn't.
我鼓捣完后就在了
It was when I finished with it.
你为什么会在这里
What the hell are you even doing here?
就玩玩游艇
A little yachting.
你就是艾莉克丝
You're Alex.
你在跟那位老太太合作
You're working with that old lady.
格特是位老朋友
Gert's a dear old friend.
得了 你有什么目的
Yeah, right. What's your angle?
没什么目的
There's no angle.
东海岸有好多格特这样
There's a lot of lovely old women like Gert…
可爱的老妇人
up and down the eastern seaboard.
我卖她们魔咒 进行招魂
I sell them charms, perform seances…
让她们跟自己死去的猫交流
so they can commune with their dead cats.
我猜猜 都是骗人的 都不是真的
And let me guess. It's all a con, none of it's real.
我提供的安慰可非常真实
The comfort I provide them is very real.
你晚上怎么睡得着
How do you sleep at night?
睡在丝绸床单上 裸着身在钱里打滚
On silk sheets, rolling naked in money.
说真的 萨姆
Really, Sam.
他对我这么冲我不意外 但你呢
I'd expect the attitude from him. But you?
你拿枪打了我
You shot me.
我也就擦伤了你
I barely grazed you.
可爱
Cute,
但有点夸张 是吧
but a bit of a drama queen, yeah?
你清楚现在的情况吧
You do know what's going on around here.
这艘鬼船是真的
This ghost ship thing, it is real.
我知道
I'm aware.
对了 谢谢你们告诉格特案子没结
Thanks for telling Gert the case wasn't solved, by the way.
- 是没结 - 她原本不知道
- It isn't. - She didn't know that.
这下那老婆子停止了付款
Now the old bag's stopped payment.
还要求知道真相
and she's demanding some real answers.
听着
Look,
你们别碍我事 别给我惹更多麻烦了
just stay out of my way before you cause any more trouble.
还是赶紧去把车取回来吧
I'd get to that car if I were you…
免得他们发现后备箱里的军火库
before they find the arsenal in the trunk.
再见
Ciao.
我可以开枪打她吗
Can I shoot her?
别当众
Not in public.
有人吗
Hello?
不 警方说他淹死了
No, the police said that he drowned, but.
但我不懂…
I don't understand how…
我很为您的丧亲遗憾 沃伦先生
I am so sorry for your loss, Mr. Warren.
可以再跟我说一遍
You know, if you could just tell me one more time.
你哥哥看到的船吗
about the ship your brother saw?
女士 我觉得他已经很痛苦了
Ma'am, I think this man's been through quite enough.
你还是走吧
You should go.
但我还有几个问题呢
But I just have a few more questions.
你没有了
No, you don't.
谢谢你抽时间
Thank you for your time.
抱歉你还得应付她 他们简直像蟑螂
Sorry you had to deal with that. They're like roaches.
我们听到你说你哥哥看到过艘船
So, uh, we heard you say your brother saw a ship?
对
Yeah, that's right.
他说过那船什么样吗
Did he tell you what it looked like?
就像老洋基快船
It was, uh, like the old Yankee Clippers,
走私船
a smuggling vessel.
气派的上桅帆 三桅船索具
A rakish topsail, a barkentine rigging.
船首上有天使艏饰像
Angel figurehead on the bow.
你哥哥看到的船你能说得这么详细
That's a lot of detail for a ship your brother saw.
我哥哥和我当时在夜间潜水
My brother and I were night diving.
我也看到那船了
I saw the ship too.
不好意思 警官 我觉得那俩人不是…
Excuse me, officers. I'm not sure those men…
好吧 我们再联系
All right. Well, we'll be in touch.
谢谢
Thank you.
看来你们取回了车
I see you got your car back.
我手里有上膛的枪呢
You really wanna come near me.
你真想靠近我吗
when I got a loaded gun in my hands?
好了 小心血压
Now, now, mind your blood pressure.
你们为什么还在这里
Why are you even still here?
你们有足够信息查到船名了
You have enough to ID the boat.
刚刚那人看到船了
That guy back there saw the ship.
是吗 怎么了
Yeah, and?
他会死的
And he's going to die.
我们得救他
So we have to save him.
真好心
How sweet.
你觉得这好笑吗
You think this is funny?
他就是炮灰
He's cannon fodder.
你们赶不及救他的 你们知道
He can't be saved in time and you know it.
是啊 可我们有灵魂
Yeah, well, see, we have souls. So.
我们要试试看
we're gonna try.
但我能找到那艘船
Yeah. Well, I'm actually gonna find the ship.
结束这一切
and put an end to this.
你们好好玩吧
But you have fun.
贝拉 你怎么会变成这样的
Bela, how'd you get like this?
怎么 爸爸抱你不够多吗
What, did Daddy not give you enough hugs or something?
我不知道
I don't know.
你爸爸抱你够多吗
Your daddy give you enough?
你少看不起我
Don't you dare look down your nose at me.
你没比我强到哪去
You're no better than I am.
我们帮助他人
We help people.
得了
Come on.
你们这么做是出于复仇和执迷
You do this out of vengeance and obsession.
你们离连环杀手也就一步之遥
You're a stone's throw from being a serial killer.
而我呢
Whereas I, on the other hand,
我收钱做事 我会把事办妥
I get paid to do a job, and I do it.
你倒是说 谁更健康
So you tell me, which is healthier?
贝拉 你走吧
Bela, why don't you just leave?
我们还有工作要做呢
We've got work to do.
是啊 你们现在0：2呢
Yeah, you're 0 for 2.
做得真好
Bang-up job so far.
有什么发现吗
Anything good?
并没有
No, not really.
两名兄弟都是杜克大学的毕业生
I mean, both brothers are Duke University grads.
没有犯罪记录
No criminal record.
有一些超速罚单
I mean, a few speeding tickets.
六年前他们继承了父亲的地产遗产
They inherited their father's real-estate fortune six years ago.
多少钱
How much?
1.12亿美元
Hundred twelve million.
- 命真好 - 是啊
- Nice life. - Yeah.
干净体面 正正当当
I mean, nice, clean, aboveboard.
他们为什么会看到船
So why'd they see the ship?
还有茜拉
Why Sheila too?
他们有什么共同点
What do they all have in common?
或许没有
Maybe nothing.
总有点什么的
Well, there's always something.
你们
You!
我们可能被发现了
Think we've been made.
你们在干什么 在监视我吗
What are you guys doing? You watching me?
先生 请冷静
Sir, calm down, please.
你们不是警察
You guys aren't cops.
警察不会穿成那样 开那样的破车
Not dressed like that. Not in that crappy car.
- 没必要这么嘴贱啊 - 听着
- No need to get nasty. - Look,
我们是警察 我们在卧底
we are cops, okay? We're undercover.
我们来是因为我们觉得你可能有危险
We're here, because we think you're in danger.
什么危险
From who?
请你冷静下来 我们谈谈吧
If you just settle down, we'll talk about it.
你们离我远点
Look, you guys, just stay away from me.
等等
Wait.
你个白痴 我们是想帮你
You moron, we're trying to help you.
- 那绝不是好事 - 是啊
- That can't be good. - No.
去拿岩盐枪
Get the salt gun.
彼得
Peter.
萨姆
Sam!
今晚起初原本只是可能略有微风
With what started out as a mild chance of breezy night,
但严酷的锋面从西北而来
is changing rapidly as a severe weather front,
让情况急转直下
is heading in from the northwest.
雷电交加和突然降雨可能…
Expect heavy lightning and thunder with sudden rainfall…
你想说 还是我来说
You wanna say it or should I?
说什么
What?
你不可能救下每个人 萨姆
You can't save everybody, Sam.
嗯 对 怎么 这样你就好受些了吗
Yeah, right. So what, you feel better now or what?
不 并没有
No, not really.
我也没有
Me neither.
你得明白
You gotta understand…
我近来觉得我谁都救不了
Just lately I feel like I can't save anybody.
天啊
Dear God.
你们是真在占房吗
Are you actually squatting?
真不错
Charming.
那么
So.
昨晚跟彼得进展如何啊
How'd things go last night with Peter?
那么好吗
That well?
如果你说「我早说了」
If you say "I told you so, "
我发誓 我会开始挥拳
I swear to God, I'll start swinging.
听着
Look,
我觉得我们三个该交交心
I think the three of us should have a heart-to-heart.
那你得有心
That's assuming you have a heart.
迪恩 得了
Dean, please.
我为之前的话道歉 好吗
I'm sorry about what I said before, okay?
我带礼物来了
I come bearing gifts.
什么礼物
Such as?
我已查到船名了
I've ID'd the ship.
是圣灵号
It's the Espirito Santo.
商用帆船 历史很丰富
A merchant sailing vessel. Quite a colorful history.
1859年 一名水手被控叛国
In 1859, a sailor was accused of treason.
他在船上的私设法庭受审 然后被绞死
He was tried aboard ship in a kangaroo court and hanged.
他当时才37
He was 37.
所以才37年一循环
Which would explain the 37-year cycle.
你还真机灵
Aren't you a sharp tack?
这里有他的照片
Photo of him somewhere.
这里
Here.
这不是我们昨晚见到的那人吗
Isn't that the customer we saw last night?
你们看到他了
You saw him?
对 就是他 但他缺了只手
Yeah. That's him, except he was missing a hand.
他的右手
His right hand.
你怎么知道
How did you know?
水手的尸体被火化了
The sailor's body was cremated,
但他们先切下了他的手 制作光荣之手
but not before they cut off his hand to make a Hand of Glory.
光荣之手
A Hand of Glory?
我上周做完
I think I got one of those.
泰式按摩后 好像享受过那个
at the end of my Thai massage last week.
迪恩 绞死的人的右手是厉害的魔物
Dean, the right hand of a hanged man is a serious occult object.
法力强大
It's very powerful.
据说是的
So they say.
并且也能算是遗骸
And officially counts as remains.
但这还是不能解释
But still, none of this explains.
鬼为何选择这些受害人
why the ghost is choosing these victims.
我告诉你吧
I'll tell you why.
谁在乎呢
Who cares?
找到那手
Find the hand,
烧了他 阻止那鬼
burn it and stop the bloody thing.
我不懂 你为什么告诉我们这些
I don't get it. Why you telling us all this?
因为我清楚手在哪
Because I know exactly where the hand is.
在哪
Where?
在海松博物馆
At the Sea Pines Museum…
作为海事历史的恐怖展品
as a macabre bit of maritime history.
但我需要帮助
But I need help.
什么样的帮助
What kind of help?
你怎么那么慢
What is taking so long?
萨姆都快到了
Sam's already halfway there.
跟他的女伴
With his date.
这太让人不爽了
So not okay with this.
你是女人吗
What are you, a woman?
快下来啊
Come down already.
好了 说吧 我样子很滑稽
All right. Get it out. I look ridiculous.
我可不会那么说
Not exactly the word I'd use.
什么
What?
等一切结束
You know, when this is over,
我们该来次愤怒性爱
we should really have angry sex.
别物化我
Don't objectify me.
走吧
Let's go.
（海松海事博物馆）
你在嚼口香糖吗
Are you chewing gum?
尽量表现得像你来过这样的场合 好吗
Try to behave as if you've lived this life before, yeah?
这会让大家嚼舌头根的 是吧 我的美男
This will get their tongues wagging, eh, my Adonis?
记住 我们是为正事而来
Just remember, we're on business.
但有时 正事也能有乐趣吧
But sometimes business can be pleasure?
是啊
Right.
那个 我可以失陪一下吗
You know, uh, could you excuse me for a moment?
好 谢谢
Great, thanks.
谢谢
Thanks.
我究竟需要陪我的女伴多久
Exactly how long do you expect me to entertain my date?
要多久是多久
As long as it takes.
听着
Look…
这里到处是保安 好吗
security all over this place. All right.
没有格特的邀请函 我们别想闯进这派对来
This is an uncrashable party without Gert's invitation, so…
我们什么都能闯 迪恩
We can crash anything, Dean.
我知道 但是
Yeah, I know, but.
这样更轻松 也更好玩
this is easier and it's a lot more entertaining.
你知道我肯做的事是有限度的吧
You know, there are limits to what I'll do, right?
他在欲擒故纵呢 真可爱
He's playing hard to get. That's cute.
走吧
Come on.
早上要把一切都告诉我
I want all the details in the morning.
谢谢
Thank you.
敬我们
To us.
私人安保吗
Private security?
我觉得不是
I don't think so.
看他们的站姿 他们是专业人士
Look at the way they're standing. They're pros.
可能是来兼职的州警
Probably state troopers moonlighting.
每个门口都有
Posted at every door too.
嗯 我们别想大摇大摆地上楼了
Yeah, I don't think we're gonna be able to just waltz upstairs.
你说怎么办
What do you suggest?
我在想呢
I'm thinking.
别累着自己了
Don't strain yourself.
有意思 某些人名不副实呢
Interesting how the legend is so much more than the man.
你有好点子 我洗耳恭听
You got any bright ideas, I'm all ears.
好吧
Okay.
亲爱的 你没事吧
Honey? Honey, are you all right?
侍者
Waiter.
我妻子对贝类严重过敏 那里面没螃蟹吧
My wife has a severe shellfish allergy. There's no crab in that?
- 没有 先生 - 是吗
- No, sir. - No?
还挺好吃的
They're excellent, by the way.
出什么事了
What seems to be the trouble?
香槟酒
Champagne.
我妻子 她酒量特别差
My wife, she's a lightweight when it comes to the sauce.
我可以让她在哪躺下
Is there somewhere I can lay her down.
缓缓吗
till she gets her sea legs back?
- 跟我来 - 好
- Follow me. - Right.
谢谢
Thank you.
来吧 你个酒鬼
Come on, you lush.
你以为她现在就是个麻烦了吗
You think she's a pain in the ass now?
跟她一起生活更烦
Try living with her.
多谢了
Thank you very much.
或许下次 实施计划前先跟我说一声
Maybe next time, give me a little heads up with your plan.
我不想让你多想
I didn't want you thinking.
你不太擅长那个
You're not very good at that.
看你啊
Look at you.
努力想说出一句俏皮话怼我
Searching for a witty rejoinder.
去你的
Screw you.
真像大文豪奥斯卡·王尔德
Very Oscar Wilde.
235室
Room 235.
在上锁玻璃箱里 有报警器
It's in a locked glass case wired for alarm.
那不成问题吧
I'm sure that won't be a problem?
艾莉克丝和你的朋友呢
Where's Alex and your friend?
他们错过好派对了
They're missing a great party.
他们肯定也自己找乐子了
I'm, ahh… I'm sure they're entertaining themselves.
淘气
Naughty.
那我们也要自己找乐子了
Then I guess we'll just have to entertain ourselves as well.
那个 凯斯太太
You know, um, Mrs. Case…
- 不对 - 抱歉
- No. - Sorry.
是凯斯女士 我不希望你误会
Ms. Case, I don't wanna give you the wrong idea.
喊我格特吧
Call me Gert.
好吧
Okay.
你让我想起我去世的丈夫
You remind me of my late husband.
他也很害羞
He was shy too.
到了下面才放开
Till we got below deck.
你真是浑身结实
You're just firm all over.
先生
Sir?
女士
Ma'am?
一切都好吗
Everything all right?
看来您好些了
Feeling better, I see.
是的 好多了 谢谢
Yes, much, thank you.
如果你们不需要这房间了
So if you're done with the room?
还没完事
Well, not exactly.
可以再给我们点时间吗
Could we have a few more minutes?
好的 女士
Yes, ma'am.
别闹了 好痒
Stop it. That tickles.
抱歉
Sorry.
内急
Nature called.
多谢照顾我妻子
Thanks for looking after my wife.
是有人照顾她了
She's being looked after all right.
有麻烦吗
Any trouble?
没什么我不能应付的
Nothing I couldn't handle.
手呢
The hand?
可以吗
May I?
不可以
No.
或许放我手包里更隐蔽
It might be more inconspicuous in my purse.
想得美
Nice try.
我只是想帮忙
Just trying to be helpful.
亲爱的
Well, sweetheart…
我不需要你帮忙
I don't need your kind of help.
天啊 这首歌好长
Man, this is one long song.
希望它永不结束
I hope it never ends.
调查怎么样了
How's the investigation going?
这种事需要时间
These things take time.
人们都在谈论沃伦兄弟的死
You know, people are talking about the Warren brothers' deaths.
奇怪
Strange.
你觉得那跟茜拉的死有关吗
Do you think it's connected to Sheila's?
嗯 我们是这么想的
Yeah. Yeah, we think so.
我觉得他们是活该
I think they had it coming, you know,
因果报应
in a Biblical sort of way.
什么意思
What do you mean?
你知道他们父亲的事吧
You know about their father.
不
No.
过来 我悄悄告诉你
Come here. I'll whisper it to you.
人们说
People say…
老头子
that the old man…
- 不是自然死亡 - 那是怎么死的
- didn't die of natural causes. - Then how?
据传 是兄弟俩干的
Rumor is the boys did it.
虽然没法证明
Nothing was ever proved but…
- 但人们还是会传话 - 好吧
- people still whisper. - Okay, okay.
那茜拉跟他们有关联吗
So did Sheila have any connection to them?
据我所知没有
Well, none that I know of.
茜拉人生里发生过什么惨剧吗
Did Sheila have any kind of tragedy in her life?
是的 还真发生过
Yes, as a matter of fact…
她十几岁时出过车祸
there was a car accident when she was a teenager.
发生了什么
What happened?
她的车翻了
Her car flipped over and.
她没事 但她表哥布莱恩死了
well, she was okay, but, uh, her cousin Brian was killed.
怎么了 这要紧吗
Why? Is that important?
好啊
Well,
还开心吗
having a nice time?
他真棒
He's delightful.
他想要我
He wants me.
我要带格特去冲个冷水澡
I'm going to get Gert into a cold shower.
好主意
Great idea.
公墓见
See you at the cemetery.
你一身骚气
You stink like sex.
你拿到了吧
You got it, right?
拜托告诉我 我不是白白被
Tell me I didn't get groped all night.
郝薇香太太摸了一晚上
by Mrs. Haversham for nothing.
我拿到了
I got it.
你说谁
Mrs. Who?
没事了 给我看看
Never mind. Just let me see it.
怎么了
What?
我要杀了她
I'm gonna kill her.
不
No.
知道吗 你是对的
You know what? You're right.
不杀她
Not gonna kill her.
缓慢折磨才是好办法
I think slow torture's the way to go.
迪恩 听着 你得放松下来
Dean, look. You gotta relax.
放松
Relax?
是啊 我放松
Yeah. Yeah, I'll relax.
真不敢相信她又胜了我们一次
Can't believe she got another one over on us.
是你
You.
什么
What?
她胜了你 不是我们
I mean, she got one over on you, not us.
谢谢 萨姆 非常有帮助
Thank you, Sam. Very helpful.
在吗 可以开门吗
Hello. Could you open up?
容我解释
Just let me explain.
我卖掉了
I sold it.
我听说它后就找好了买家
I had a buyer lined up as soon as I knew it existed.
所以骗我们去慈善舞会是为了…
So the whole reason for us going to the charity ball was…?
我需要个掩护
I needed a cover.
你们正方便了我
You were convenient.
你卖给了买家 那去买回来啊
Look, you sold it to a buyer, just go buy it back.
已经在漂洋过海了 来不及要回来了
It's halfway across the ocean. I can't get it back in time.
什么来不及了
In time for what?
你怎么了 贝拉
What's going on with you, Bela?
你像是见鬼了
You look like you've seen a ghost.
我看到船了
I saw the ship.
你什么
You what?
要知道
You know, I…
我知道你是个不道德的骗子小贼贱人
I knew you were an immoral, thieving, con-artist bitch.
但就当我以为我对你的看法
But just when I thought my opinion of you.
不会更差了
couldn't get any lower…
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
我们查明鬼魂的动机了
We figured out the spirit's motive.
这是鬼船的船长
This is the captain of our ship…
绞死了那个鬼魂的人
the one who hung our ghost boy.
怎么了
So?
他们是兄弟
So they were brothers.
真像该隐和亚伯
Very Cain and Abel.
所以这个鬼
So now our spirit,
他针对的是一种特定的目标
he's going after a very specific kind of target.
害死了自己亲人的人
People who've spilled their own family's blood.
先是茜拉
See, first there was Sheila,
她在车祸中害死了表哥
who killed her cousin in a car accident.
然后是沃伦兄弟
Then the Warren brothers…
为谋遗产杀害了父亲
who murdered their father for the inheritance.
现在又是你
And now you.
天啊
My God.
所以是谁 贝拉
So who was it, Bela?
你杀了谁
Who'd you kill?
爸爸吗
Was it Daddy?
你妹妹吗
Your little sis, maybe?
不关你事
It's none of your business.
是啊
No.
没错
Right.
那祝你人生愉快
Well, have a nice life.
你仅剩的人生
You know, whatever's left of it.
萨姆 我们走
Sam. Let's go.
你们不能丢下我不管
You can't just leave me here.
看我们的
Watch us.
求你们
Please.
我需要你们帮忙
I need your help.
我们帮忙
Our help?
两个连环杀手怎么能帮你呢
Now, how could a couple of serial killers possibly help you?
好吧 那话有些过分了 我承认
Okay, that was a bit harsh. I admit it.
但我也不该为此而死
But it doesn't warrant a death sentence.
那不是你要死的原因
That's not why you're gonna die.
你做了什么 贝拉
What did you do, Bela?
你不会理解的
You wouldn't understand.
没人理解
No one did.
算了
Never mind.
我还是像以往一样 自己解决吧
I'll just do what I've always done and I'll deal with it myself.
你知道你刚卖掉了
You do realize you just sold.
唯一能救你命的东西
the only thing that could save your life?
我知道
I'm aware.
其实
Well…
那或许不是唯一的
Maybe not the only thing.
你真觉得这能行吗
Do you really think this is gonna work?
完全不觉得
Almost definitely not.
萨姆
Sammy.
快点读吧
Better start reading.
靠紧我
Stay close.
你身后
Behind you!
萨姆 快读
Sammy, read faster.
你绞死了我
You hanged me.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你的亲弟弟
Your own brother.
真对不起
I'm so sorry.
你们该知道锁门
You boys should learn to lock your doors.
谁都可能冲进来
Anyone could just barge in.
这不是有人进来了
Anyone just did.
你是来道别的 还是说谢谢的
You come to say goodbye or thank you?
我是来做个了断的
I've come to settle affairs.
满足那鬼魂的心愿 把他哥哥给他
Giving the spirit what he really wanted, his own brother.
真聪明 萨姆
Very clever, Sam.
给
So here.
这是一万美元
It's 10, 000.
应该够了
That should cover it.
我不喜欢欠人什么
I don't like being in anyone's debt.
所以掏一万
So ponying up 10 grand.
对于你比说声「谢谢」要简单吗
is easier for you than a simple "thank you"?
你真是有毛病
You're so damaged.
彼此彼此
Takes one to know one.
再见了 伙计们
Goodbye, lads.
她真有风格
She got style.
这你得承认
You gotta give her that.
大概吧
I suppose.
迪恩 我们都不知道这钱怎么来的
You know, Dean, we don't know where this money's been.
对
No.
但我知道这钱要怎么花
But I know where it's going.
不是吧
Seriously?
大西洋城吗
Atlantic City?
当然
Hell, yeah.
玩玩轮盘赌 永远压黑
Play some roulette, always bet on black.
听着 我想了想
Listen, I've been doing some thinking…
我想告诉你 我理解你为什么那么做
I want you to know I understand why you did it.
我理解你为什么去找十字路口恶魔
I understand why you went after the Crossroads Demon.
如果情况调过来
You know, the situation was reversed,
我大概也会那么做
I guess I'd have done the same thing.
我不瞎
I mean, I'm not blind.
我看得到这整件事对你的伤害
I see what you're going through with this whole deal.
我要走了什么的
Me going away and all that.
但你会没事的
But you're gonna be okay.
是吗
You think so?
嗯 你会继续猎魔
Yeah, you'll keep hunting.
过你的日子
You know, you'll live your life.
你比我坚强 是的
You're stronger than me. You are.
是的 你会过去的
You are. You'll get over it.
但我要说 对不起 抱歉我
But I want you to know I'm sorry. I'm sorry for.
让你经受这一切 真的
putting you through all this, I am.
知道吗 迪恩 去你的吧
You know what, Dean? Go screw yourself.
- 什么 - 我不想听你道歉
- What? - I don't want an apology from you.
对了 我是个大人了 我能照顾好自己
And by the way, I'm a big boy now. I can take care of myself.
不好意思了
Well, excuse me.
所以你能不能别再担心我了
So would you quit worrying about me?
这正是问题所在
I mean, that's the whole problem in the first place.
我不希望你担心我 迪恩
I don't want you to worry about me, Dean.
我要你担心你自己
I want you to worry about you.
我要你在乎你要死了这件事
I want you to give a crap that you're dying.
就这样吗
So that's it?
你不想再说点什么吗
Nothing else to say from you?
或许我要玩双骰子赌博
I think maybe I'll play craps.